我们之前没来这里表演过 你们还要更多吗？！
I didn't hear what you were saying
我不想听到你说什么
I live on raw emotion baby
宝贝，我的感情并不成熟
I answer questions never maybe
我也许无法回答那些问题
And I'm not kind if you betray me
不过如果你背叛了我，我绝对不会客气
So who the hell are you to save me
你从地狱拯救了我
I never would have made it babe
我不会让别人得到你
If you needed love
在你需要爱的时候
Well then ask for love
请你去追寻它
Could have given love
我渴望得到爱
Now I'm taking
那么此时此刻我得到了爱
And it's not my fault
这并不是我的错
Cause you both deserve
为了你什么都值得
What's coming now
当它来临的时候
So don't say a word
就不要说什么
Wake up call
一个使我了解真相的电话
Caught you in the morning with another one in my bed
让我在今天上午在床上亲手抓到你和另一个人
Don't you care about me anymore?
你不再关心我了吗？
Don't you care about me? I don't think so
不关心我了吗？我不这么认为
Six foot tall
6英尺的身高
Came without a warning so I had to shoot him dead
突然的冲了过来，我不得不杀了他
He won't come around here anymore
他永远都不会再来这里了
Come around here? I don't think so
我不认为他还会来到这里
Would have bled to make you happy
流出来的血液会使你感到开心么
You didn't need to treat me that (way)
你没有必要这样做
And now you beat me at my own game
你可以对我感到不满
And now I'm finally sleeping soundly
现在我终于可以安心了
And your lover's screaming loudly I hear a sound and hit the ground
你的爱人在尖叫声中倒在了地面
If you needed love
在你需要爱的时候
Well then ask for love
请你去追寻它
Could have given love
我渴望得到爱
Now I'm taking love
那麽此时此刻我得到了爱
And it's not my fault
这并不是我的错
Cause you both deserve
为了你什么都值得
What's coming now
当它来临的时候
So don't say a word
就不要说什么
Wake up call
一个使我了解真相的电话
Caught you in the morning with another one in my bed
让我在今天上午在床上亲手抓到你和另一个人
Don't you care about me anymore?
你不再关心我了吗？
Don't you care about me? I don't think so
不关心我了吗？我不这么认为
Six foot tall
6英尺的身高
Came without a warning so I had to shoot him dead
突然的冲了过来，我不得不杀了他
He won't come around here anymore
他永远都不会再来这里了
Come around here?
他还会来到这里？
I don't feel so bad
我并不觉得糟糕
I'm so sorry darling
我很抱歉，亲爱的
Did I do the wrong thing?
我到底做错了什么？
Oh, what was I thinking?
哦，我到底在想什么？
Is his heart still beating?
难道他的心仍在跳动？
Woah oh ohh
哇~~哦~~~哦~~
I don't feel so bad, I don't feel so bad
我并不觉得糟糕  我并不觉得糟糕
Wake up call
一个使我了解真相的电话
Caught you in the morning with another one in my bed
让我在今天上午在床上亲手抓到你和另一个人
Don't you care about me anymore?
你不再关心我了吗？
care about me? I don't think so
关心我？我不这么认为
Six foot tall
6英尺的身高
Came without a warning so I had to shoot him dead
突然的冲了过来，我不得不杀了他
He won't come around here anymore
他永远都不会再来这里了
Come around here？I don't feel so bad
他还会来到这里？我并不觉得糟糕
I don't feel so bad
我并不觉得糟糕
don't feel so bad
并不觉得糟糕
I don't feel so bad
我并不觉得糟糕